Guide to the Mildred Martin Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 8. Audiovisual materials
  - Tien Wu1969, 1 audiocassette: use copy + 1 audiocassette: master (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Donaldina Cameron & Tien Wu, 1967, 1 audiocassette: use copy + 1 audiocassette: master (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lorna Logan & Dick Wigman, 1969 Jan. 8, 1 audiocassette: use copy + 1 audiocassette: master (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mae Wong, 1969, 2 audiocassettes (2 of 20: use copy + 2 audiocassettes (2 of 2): master (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Mae Wong, 1969, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Caroline Bailey & Allan Cameron, 1971 Sept. 23, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Donaldina Cameron / Mildred Crowl Martin, 1978 Apr. 10, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Mitchell Park Library speech [on] Donaldina Cameron, Palo Alto / Mildred Crowl Martin, 1978 Jan. 26, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Dori, 1971 Feb. 25, and, Cameron House speech to guides / Mildred Martin, 1976 Nov. 22, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Ken Cameron, and, Barbara Knopes, 1981 Mar. 17, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Mae Wong, and, Martin, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Interview with Donaldina Cameron / by Mildred Martin, and, Interview with Tien Wu, 1967, 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Donaldina Cameron, and, Evelyn Miller Brown, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Speech to AAUW on Evelyn Miller Brown, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Donaldina Cameron House - a vision of hope in Chinatown. -- San Francisco, Calif.: Cameron House, n.d., 1 videocassette: col. VHS (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Tien Wu, 1969, 1 audiotape: reel-to-reel (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Donaldina Cameron and Tien Wu, 1967, 1 audiotape: reel-to-reel (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Mae Wong, 1969, 1 audiotape: reel-to-reel (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - [Unidentified], n.d., 1 audiotape: reel-to-reel. Garbled (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Series 9. Computer files
  Contains computer files for the various chapters of a work entitled on the diskettes simply as "Mark's Dictionary".
  - Mark's Dictionary: Chapter 1 thru 6, n.d., 10 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Contains two copies of each chapter.
  - Mark's Dictionary: all thru 4, n.d., 5 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Mark's Dictionary: Chapter 7, 8, 9, 10 (x2), n.d., 6 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mark's Dictionary: Chapter 11 thru 21: originalsn.d., 9 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Mark's Dictionary: Chapter 11 thru 21: copiesn.d., 11 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mark's Dictionary: miscellaneousn.d., 4 diskettes; 5.25 (Box 22, Folder 6)